<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Maize</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="other">Preventing maize diseases in gardens is crucial for ensuring healthy plant growth and maximizing crop yield. Key strategies include practicing crop rotation, selecting disease-resistant varieties, planting healthy seed, providing proper spacing, maintaining good sanitation practices, managing irrigation effectively, controlling pests, and monitoring for early signs of disease. By implementing these preventive measures, gardeners can reduce the risk of maize diseases and promote successful cultivation.</string>
    <string name="mlb">Maize Lethal Necrosis is a devastating disease that affects maize plants, causing significant crop losses worldwide. It is characterized by the yellowing and wilting of leaves, stunting of plant growth, and eventually leading to plant death. The disease is caused by a combination of two viruses: Maize Chlorotic Mottle Virus (MCMV) and Sugarcane Mosaic Virus (SCMV). These viruses are transmitted to maize plants through insect vectors, such as aphids or leafhoppers. Maize Lethal Necrosis poses a major threat to maize production as it can rapidly spread within fields and neighboring areas. To prevent and manage the disease, various strategies are employed, including the use of virus-free seed, crop rotation, insect control measures, and early detection and destruction of infected plants. Additionally, developing resistant maize varieties through breeding programs and promoting awareness among farmers about the disease and its management are crucial steps in mitigating the impact of Maize Lethal Necrosis on agricultural productivity.</string>
    <string name="hlt">Preventing maize diseases in gardens is crucial for ensuring healthy plant growth and maximizing crop yield. Key strategies include practicing crop rotation, selecting disease-resistant varieties, planting healthy seed, providing proper spacing, maintaining good sanitation practices, managing irrigation effectively, controlling pests, and monitoring for early signs of disease. By implementing these preventive measures, gardeners can reduce the risk of maize diseases and promote successful cultivation. </string>
    <string name="msv">Maize Streak is a viral disease that affects maize plants and poses a significant threat to maize production. Prevention and treatment of Maize Streak Virus (MSV) primarily involve implementing various management practices. To prevent the spread of MSV, farmers can employ cultural practices such as planting disease-resistant maize varieties, practicing crop rotation, and using certified disease-free seeds. Additionally, controlling the population of leafhopper vectors, which transmit the virus, through insecticide application and the use of physical barriers can help reduce the spread of the disease. In terms of treatment, unfortunately, there are no effective chemical or biological treatments available for MSV-infected plants. Therefore, early detection and removal of infected plants are crucial to prevent the disease from spreading to healthy plants. Additionally, practicing good sanitation and hygiene in the field, including proper disposal of crop residues, can help reduce the risk of MSV infection. Overall, a combination of preventive measures, vigilant monitoring, and prompt action is essential in managing and minimizing the impact of Maize Streak Virus on maize crops.</string>
    <string name="class1">Healthy</string>
    <string name="class2">Maize Lethal Necrosis</string>
    <string name="class3">Maize Streak Virus</string>
    <string name="class4">Other</string>
</resources>